<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Atazzo</title><link>https://atazzo.com/</link><description>Recent content on Atazzo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 17:26:11 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://atazzo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Process</title><link>https://atazzo.com/features/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 08:32:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atazzo.com/features/process/</guid><description>Rapid growth introduces additional complexity in both technological and organizational structure. We help companies design and implement lightweight processes that help sustain and increase successful growth.</description></item><item><title>Technology</title><link>https://atazzo.com/features/tech/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 08:32:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atazzo.com/features/tech/</guid><description>Whether it&amp;rsquo;s Data Science and Machine Learning or scalability challenges with technology architecture, we help growing companies with their unique technology challenges. We have extensive experience in high-performance systems and real-time systems in a variety of industries.</description></item><item><title>Adam Drake</title><link>https://atazzo.com/adam-drake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atazzo.com/adam-drake/</guid><description>Adam Drake leads technical business transformations in global and multi-cultural environments. He has served as a White House Presidential Innovation Fellow, worked with sucessful enterprise and scale-up technology companies all over the world, and is an IEEE Senior Member.
Adam&amp;rsquo;s professional background spans a variety of industries including e-commerce, online travel, online marketing, financial services, healthcare, and oil and gas. His recognition as a Senior Member of the Institute for Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE) places him in the top 10% of over 400,000 members in over 160 countries.</description></item><item><title>Footer</title><link>https://atazzo.com/footer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://atazzo.com/footer/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re a dedicated team of technical professionals serving global clients. Our expertise ranges from developing leaders to designing full stack technological solutions for highly challenging business problems.
To contact us, please email info (.at.) atazzo (.dot.) com.</description></item></channel></rss>